



# **Summary**

I'm Pourya Dehghan a Software engineer with the background of petrochemical engineering educations and designing experience.. I started my coding journey two years ago, I feel really lucky that my job is my biggest hobbies. I'm eager to make the leap and continue refining my skills with the right company.

# **Skills**

HTML, CSS, javaScript, React, python, Django,

MongoDB, Boostrap, PostrageSQL, Github, PhotoShop, Lightroom

# **Education and Training**

Some College (No Degree)
General Assembly

Remote

Software Engineer

#### **Bachelor of Science**

Marvdasht Azad University
Petrochemical Engineering, 04/2013

# **Experience**

## **General Assembly**

Software Engineer | Remote 05/2021 to 08/2021

Learning programming and computer science fundamentals, and creating full stack applications.

#### Uber

Driver | Atlanta, GA 04/2017 to 06/2021

#### Yerce

Photo Editor & Designer 06/2014 to 12/2016

Photographer

Designing Wedding albums.

## Languages

# English: Professional Native/ Bilingual Turkish: Limited

# Websites, Portfolios, Profiles

- https://www.pouryadegan.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/degan90/
- https://github.com/Degan90